How much you give me to eat
this whole jar of olives?
I won't give you anything,
but you'll owe me $2.95.
Done.
I need an atlas!
Why? Do you have a report due?
I have a date
with diplomat I met...
...while I was giving free massages
outside the U. N.
And I don't know where his country is.
Let's start with
the free massages at the U.N.
It's my new thing. I figure,
"Bodies at peace make peace."
You might just get
the first Nobel Prize in rubbing.
So what country is this guy from?
There's a "g" in there.
Where's that?
In your atlas!
I don't have an atlas.
But wait, I do have a globe.
Hold on.
So what's this guy like?
Well, he's very...
...dashing, you know?
And very, very sophisticated.
And he doesn't speak English...
... but his translator says
he totally gets me.
Okay, here you go.
What is this?
It's a globe.
And a pencil sharpener.
Need anything copied?
I'm going to the Xerox place.
No, thanks.
Just give me anything
I can make two of.
If you have nothing to copy,
why go there?
Are you just gonna gawk
at that girl...
...with the bellybutton ring again?
You wanna come?
The One Where
Ross and Rachel Take a Break
Come on, Chloe. Finish with
your customer first.
Come on, Chloe.
Come on, Chloe!
Can I help you?
We're having second thoughts
about our copying needs.
And we'll need more time
to think about it.
Chloe, switch with me. Some guys
have a crush on you.
Okay, that hurt us.
Hi, guys. I haven't seen you
since this morning.
Well...
...you know.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Both of us?
Maybe. Does that scare you?
Relax. Isaac's deejaying
at The Philly.
-You should come.
-We'll be there.
Great. I'll see you then.
All right! Rock on.
He says that walking with you makes
this strange city feel like home.
Me too. Although this city
is my home.
So that's dumb, what I said.
Don't tell him I said that.
You make something up.
Nice! Thank you.
This is me, here.
Your eyes are very pretty.
Thank you very much.
Oh, thank you.
He would like to kiss you.
You don't have to do that now.
No, no, not him!
No, you don't.
The moment's over.
There it is, right there.
It's small.
Yeah, but Sergei said
it took the Germans six weeks...
...to get all the way across it.
So you had fun?
Except for, you know,
when you're on a date...
...and you're getting along great...
... but the guy's translator
keeps getting in the way?
Is Rach in her room?
She's still at work,
but she said to call her.
Is she gonna cancel on me again?
How could she do this?
What about our anniversary?
This is the extent of my knowledge
on the subject.
"Call Rachel."
What's that on the bottom?
That's my doodle of
a ladybug with a top hat.
She's fancy.
-Hey, honey.
-Oh, hi.
What's going on?
Shipping had a disaster.
I've gotta get this order in.
I'm so sorry, but it looks like
I'll be here all night.
What? Well, how about
I come up there?
No, honey, please.
I just have too much to deal with.
Anyway, I'm going out
with Sergei again tonight, and....
Could you be the translator's date...
...so that when we want to be alone...
...you two can split off?
You know, he's kind of cute.
Like, "really kind of cute"?
Or "kind of cute" like your friend
Spackle-Back Larry?
Don't call him that.
His name is Spackle-Back Harry.
Maybe we should get going.
What time did Chloe say
to get there?
-10:30.
-What time is it now?
4:30.
So we'll hang out.
Remember when she brought up
that thing about the three of us?
Yes, vividly.
-She was kidding about that, right?
-Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, I think so.
God, it'd be weird if that situation
presented itself tonight.
Yeah, I mean...
...what would we do?
Dude, I don't know.
She was kidding.
She was....
Just in case, we should have
some ground rules.
Yeah. For sure.
You probably want the first one to be,
"Never open your eyes."
Because you don't
want to be doing something...
...and then look up, right?
And see something that
you don't want to be seeing.
Good call. Nice.
Hold it! Hold it!
What if my eyes are closed, and...
...and my hand is out there....
Okay, eyes open at all times!
How do we decide where we...
...you know, each would...
...you know...
... be?
Right. Well, you know,
we could flip for it.
I guess. But like,
what's heads and what's tails?
If you don't know that,
I don't want to do this with you.
No, no. I am looking
at a purchase order here...
...that shows we
ordered the Riviera bikini...
...in a variety of sizes and colors
What does it matter what I'm wearing?
Could I speak to your supervisor?
Thank you.
Hi.
My God!
What are you doing here?
Well, you said
you couldn't go out, so....
You brought a picnic!
What a boyfriend.
That's it. On Monday, I start
wearing makeup.
Honey, this is very nice,
but I've got a crisis.
But I've got couscous!
Honey,
I know it's our anniversary...
... but I told you on the phone,
I don't have time to stop.
You don't have to stop.
I'm invisible. I'm not here.
Yeah, but I don't
Who approved that order?
Well, there is no Mark Robinson
in this office.
-Get Mark on the phone!
-I love Mark. Do you know him?
Let me check that
with what I've got.
See, 038 is not the number
for this store. 038 is Atlanta.
Pepper?
None for me.
Okay, sorry!
Sorry. As I was saying,
the store number is wrong.
And I'm sorry, but
Oh, my God!
I have to call you back.
I've got Shemp in my office.
-What are you doing?
-I'm sorry.
But somebody's off the phone!
How about a glass of wine...
... by the fire?
I can get it going again....
You're not listening.
I don't have time to stop.
-You don't have 10 minutes?
-I don't have 10 minutes!
-Sophie, does she have 10 minutes?
-I told you, I don't!
Don't yell. This is
the most I've seen you all week.
Look, I cannot do this right now.
I've got a deadline!
Go home and we'll talk later.
-Yeah, but wait!
-Goodbye!
Actually, that's our three-hole punch.
Hi.
Look, about what happened earlier
I completely understand.
You were stressed.
I was gonna give you a chance
to apologize to me.
For letting you throw me
out of your office?
You had no right
coming down to my office.
You do not bring a picnic basket
to somebody's work...
... unless they're a park ranger!
Excuse me for wanting to be with
my girl on our anniversary.
Boy, what an ass am l!
But I told you
I didn't have the time!
Well, you never have the time.
I don't feel like I have
a girlfriend anymore.
Do you want me to quit my job...
...so you can feel like
you have a girlfriend?
It would nice if you'd realize
that it's just a job.
Just a job?
It's the first time in my life
I'm doing something I care about!
The first time
I'm doing something I'm good at!
If you don't get that
I get that, and I'm happy for you.
But I'm tired of dating your answering
machine! I don't know what to do!
Well, neither do l!
Is this about Mark?
Oh, my God!
Okay, it's not.
I cannot keep having this same fight
over and over again.
You're making this too hard.
I'm making this too hard?
What should I do?
I don't know!
I don't know! Look...
...maybe we should just take a break!
Fine, you're right.
Let's take a break. Let's cool off.
Let's get some frozen yogurt
or something.
A break from us.
advances in collating
in the past five years.
We just got in an X-5000, you know?
The X-5000 makes an X-50
look like a T-71.
It's the dinosaur guy!
-Hi, Ross!
-Hi, Chloe.
I want you to meet
some friends of mine.
He's my hero. He'll want
to blow stuff up 400 percent.
We say we don't do that. He says,
"You gotta." Know what? We did it.
Now anytime anybody wants 400,
we just say, "Let's Ross it!"
And that's the only color
that comes in.
Yo, Chloe! Do you have a quarter
for the condom machine?
What are you doing? I thought
tonight's your anniversary dinner.
A little change of plans.
We're gonna break up instead.
And I can speak a little French.
Why? What did I say?
Well, you just asked if I wanted
to go to bed with you tonight.
Oh, my God!
No wonder I get such great service
at Cafe Maurice.
IKnock, knock, knock.
Hi. Could you please tell Sergei
that I was fascinated...
...by what Boutros Boutros-Ghali said
in the Times?
You didn't say
"Boutros Boutros-Ghali."
Boutros Boutros-Ghali.
He says he was too.
Interesting.
So I was wondering
Before you get all talky again...
...could you also please
tell Sergei...
...that I really like his suit.
He said, "Thank you.
You look pretty tonight.
Your hair, golden like the sun."
So you're a chef?
I'm also thinking of opening up
my own restaurant.
Really?
Could I talk to you
behind my menu?
What are you doing?
Well, I was having a conversation.
Misha's so interested in you, Sergei
and I haven't been able to talk at all.
You want me to sit silently,
while you three converse?
That would be great.
Thank you.
Hi. It's Mark.
What? Is it my breath?
Sorry. I just thought
you were somebody else.
I was just gonna leave a message.
Isn't tonight your anniversary dinner?
Rach? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You wanna talk?
I can come over.
Really, no. Please.
That's okay.
All right. I'm coming over
with Chinese food.
I'm not hungry.
It's for me.
Bye.
-So what'll you do?
-What can I do?
One person wants to break up,
you break up.
No way. This is you guys.
Call her and work it out.
We just had this huge fight.
Don't I have to wait awhile?
It isn't like swimming after you eat.
Pick up the phone!
You know that
swimming thing is a myth.
Tell that to my Uncle Lenny.
Why? What happened to him?
Nothing. He just really
believes in that.
Then we got into this big fight
It was awful.
I told him he treats me like
a park ranger, something....
And then...
... I told him
I wanted to take a break.
I don't want to take a break.
I'm sorry.
Egg roll?
And then I called him and
he wasn't there.
He's probably just out.
Thank you, that's very helpful.
I'm glad you came over.
Hi, it's me.
Oh, I'm so glad you called.
Really?
This is crazy. Don't you think
we can work on this?
What do you want to drink?
Who's that?
Nobody?
Is it okay if I finish
the apple juice?
Is that Mark?
Honey, he just came over
Yeah, got it!
Hey, Dinosaur Guy!
Look at you, so sad.
Come dance.
That's okay. Thanks.
You don't have to smile.
You just have to dance.
I don't feel like dancing.
I feel like having a drink, okay?
Two beers!
And the vet said it was time.
And so from half a world away...
...while my mother
held the phone to his ear...
... I said goodbye to my dog...
...in seven languages.
-Could I have a tissue?
-Oh, sure.
I just hope you don't accidentally...
...suck it up through your nose
and choke on it.
Sergei would like to apologize
for my behavior tonight.
Well, tell him, "Apology accepted."
Unbelievable. For the first time in
years, someone wants to talk to me.
But do you think he would
let me enjoy that? No!
You silly diplomat.
Why don't you learn some English?
Excuse me, but isn't he paying
for your dinner?
The man's dog just died.
I have just resigned my post.
Will you accompany me
to the Rainbow Room?
I have diplomatic coupons.
It would be my pleasure.
My guy has coupons.
Your guy can't even say "coupons."
Plate.
Plate! Yes! Plate!
See, we don't need them.
I like this song.
Well, you're practically
dancing, already.
Why don't you just do it over here?
What are you, married?
Because that's okay.
Oh, be home, be home, be home....
You're not home.
Still no smile?
Miss American Pie
Ameri-can.
It's a very hard language.
Let's do it again.